momsview.com 2003-12-07

# Baby Freebies, Free Bibs, Bottles, Webpages, Diapers

Privacy Policy Your privacy is important to us at Momsview.com. We do not collect personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. We collect, process and use personal information only for performing the relevant service selected by you. These services include advertisements on the Site and in the newsletters, the Site's link exchange, Board Montitor agreement, and contests run by this Site. That information will be gathered when you come onto our site to: provide feedback, voluntarily provide content for publication on the Site, request product information, purchase a product or service, request contact from a Momsview.com Chat.com representative; or participate in a contest on this Site. Your information is only released to perform such services and only that information which is necessary to provide such services. The personal information that may be gathered includes your name, fax, telephone number, address and e-mail address. You may also be asked for further information about yourself such as your industry type, your company name and job title, and your function in your company. The type of information that is collected and subsequenlty used on the Site will be dependent on the type of service the information is needed for . For example, your contact information will be necessary on a Rent-A-Page Ad. When you purchase products such as advertising from this Site, we DO NOT collect your credit card number and its expiration date. This is all done through a third party secure server and this Site is not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party link used or provided by this Site, such as PayPal. Your personal information WILL NOT be sold, exchanged or redistributed to anyone for any reason, unless permission is granted by you in writing. Whenever you give out personal information online , via the Discussion boards or Chat Room, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While this Site strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you voluntarily disclose online; you make such disclosures at your own risk. Feona Distler and MomsView.com's participation in any advertising is solely that of providing advertising space and linking.   
Feona Distler and MomsView.com cannot and does not investigate the legitimacy, validity, legality of any item listed, and expressly disclaims any responsibility or liability arising out of or relating to any item listed including: - \- 1) the legality of the ad/offer   
2) the performance or conduct of the advertiser/merchant,   
3) any damages or injury that may result from the ad/offer listed.   
Our web sites and our newsletter are simply listings of freebies and  
trial offers found, and it is the responsibility of the subscribers to  
determine validity of the individual sites/offers.
